<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writeups on Duma Labs</title>
    <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writeups on Duma Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Phishy v1</title>
      <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/phishy-v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/phishy-v1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up for investigation “Phishy v1” lab on Blue Team Labs Online. This lab is retired, so while completing it does not provide points that contribute towards the live leaderboard, but it does count towards achievements and write-ups are permitted to be made publicly available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;❗&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;WARNING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The website and kit in this lab is REAL. Exercise caution when interacting with the malicious website and do not enter any sensitive information!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonyx</title>
      <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/nonyx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/nonyx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up for the retired Blue Team Labs Online investigation &amp;lsquo;Nonyx&amp;rsquo;.&#xA;The investigation is now retired, so it can still be completed towards achievements, and public write-ups are now permitted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Purify Black Energy 2 from Shadowbrook’s digital infrastructure by reverse-engineering the malware’s code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-of-investigation&#34;&gt;Process of Investigation:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the investigation environment loads, there are a few files and directories already on the desktop. There were directories for the applications CyberChef and volatility, and files readme.txt file, and a &amp;lsquo;BlackEnergy.vnem&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee of the Year</title>
      <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/employee-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 01:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/employee-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up for the retired Blue Team Labs Online challenge &amp;lsquo;Employee of the Year&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a Friday evening when you were in a mood to celebrate your weekend, your team was alerted with a new RCE vulnerability actively being exploited in the wild. You have been tasked with analysing and researching the sample to collect information for the weekend team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-of-investigation&#34;&gt;Process of Investigation:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This challenge took some additional work before I could start work on the investigation. After downloading and extracting the contents of the challenge zip file, there was just one file, &amp;lsquo;recoverfiles.dd&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reaper</title>
      <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/reaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/reaper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up of the retired &amp;lsquo;Sherlock&amp;rsquo; challenge, Reaper. Sherlocks are investigative challenges, to help develop and test defensive cybersecurity skills. Retired content on Hack The Box, has write-ups enabled, and I think that this would be a good opportunity to work through a challenge, and practice my documentation while working through the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our SIEM alerted us to a suspicious logon event which needs to be looked at immediately. The alert details were that the IP Address and the Source Workstation name were a mismatch. You are provided a network capture and event logs from the surrounding time around the incident timeframe. Correlate the given evidence and report back to your SOC Manager.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Planet&#39;s Prestige</title>
      <link>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/the-planets-prestige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 22:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dumalabs.uk/cybersecurity/writeups/the-planets-prestige/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up for &amp;lsquo;The Planet&amp;rsquo;s Prestige&amp;rsquo;. This is a CTF-Like challenge, that is now &amp;lsquo;Retired&amp;rsquo;, on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://blueteamlabs.online/home&#34;&gt;Blue Team Labs Online&lt;/a&gt; cybersecurity practice and challenge platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When challenges are retired, this means that leaderboard points are not awarded, but then write-ups for the challenge are permitted to be made public.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I have only recently received a certification for cybersecurity, and I am using this platform as part of my learning experience to complete challenges and tasks. This is in an effort to better prepare me as I start to look into progressing in to the field of cybersecurity for a career.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
