<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Duma Labs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Duma Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:02:41 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chariot of the Gods 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:02:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;system&#34;&gt;System:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alien RPG.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;campaign&#34;&gt;Campaign:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chariot of the Gods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;session&#34;&gt;Session:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Episode 1:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Pilot&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; 04 April 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cast&#34;&gt;Cast&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Corporate Liaison John J. Wilson - Jarrad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cargo Handler Lyron Cham - Aoife&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;act-1&#34;&gt;Act 1:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The year is 2183, and the USCSS Montero is transporting 200,000 tonnes of Tritium gas from Anchorpoint station through The Gauntlet, a trade route in the Frontier, to Sutters World.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the Montero&amp;rsquo;s sensors developed a glitch before you left Anchorpoint, the cargo run had been without incident.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chariot of the Gods 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:02:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;system&#34;&gt;System:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alien RPG.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;campaign&#34;&gt;Campaign:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chariot of the Gods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;session&#34;&gt;Session:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Episode 2:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Emergence&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; 18 April 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cast&#34;&gt;Cast&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Corporate Liaison John J. Wilson - Jarrad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cargo Handler Lyron Cham - Aoife&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Technician Kayla Rye - Sassrass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dim emergency lighting of the Cronus bridge cast long shadows as the Montero crew surveyed the inert systems. Life support flickered, indicating several cryo-chambers were occupied, yet the minimal power prevented any detailed analysis. The stale air hung heavy, a testament to the offline filtration. Rye, ever pragmatic, suggested a detour to the air scrubbers before restoring full power. Activating them prematurely, he cautioned, could turn the units into lethal electrocution traps if any faults lay within.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chariot of the Gods 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:02:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ttrpg/alien/chariot-of-the-gods-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;system&#34;&gt;System:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alien RPG.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;campaign&#34;&gt;Campaign:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chariot of the Gods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;session&#34;&gt;Session:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Episode 3:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Countdown&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; 14 May 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cast&#34;&gt;Cast&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Corporate Liaison John J. Wilson - Jarrad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pilot Leah Davis - Cayden&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The creature, covered in blood, seeing itself surrounded, and the exit blocked, runs further into the bridge, up the wall and crashes through one of the air vents. Several of the Montero crew back away, while Wilson has a look at Dr. Cooper. Dr. Cooper has a rash over his hands and neck, and in his pocket, he had a syringe that contained a black liquid.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;This page is currently under construction. Please check back later!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll be adding my portfolio of photography here soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;hello-im-emma&#34;&gt;Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Emma.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m an experienced IT professional with over 7 years of technical support expertise and a fervent passion for modern IT environments. My journey in the world of technology began in the mid 1980’s when we got an Acorn Electron computer, and had to load games from cassette tapes, or type in all the code manually, from magazines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That early passion never faded, and developed in to building PCs, configuring home networks and getting some basic knowledge of programming with C++ and Pascal, in the late 1990’s. Since then, I’ve continued with that passion, always wanted to learn and experience more. I’ve experienced more with programming languages C# and Java, I’ve honed a robust understanding of virtualisation technologies including Hyper-V, VMware ESXi &amp;amp; Workstation, Oracle VirtualBox, and Proxmox.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishy V1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/phishy-v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:36:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/phishy-v1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have been sent a phishing link. Sadly the threat actor doesn’t know who they were dealing with. From only one phishing link find out all you can about the person responsible and bring them to justice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;❗ &lt;strong&gt;WARNING&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;The website and kit in this lab is REAL.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Exercise caution when interacting with the malicious website and do not enter any sensitive information!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ℹ️ &lt;strong&gt;INFO&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;As the website referenced is a live website, any references, or links to URLs, IP addresses etc in this write-up have been ‘defanged’. I do not hold any responsibility for anyone using these links.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonyx</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/nonyx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:33:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/nonyx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Purify Black Energy 2 from Shadowbrook’s digital infrastructure by reverse-engineering the malware’s code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-of-investigation&#34;&gt;Process of Investigation:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the investigation environment loads, there are a few files and directories already on the desktop. There were directories for the applications CyberChef and volatility, and files &lt;code&gt;readme.txt&lt;/code&gt; file, and &lt;code&gt;BlackEnergy.vnem&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The readme file was small, and only contained the text:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-code&#34; data-lang=&#34;code&#34;&gt;WinXPSP2x86 is the profile you must use.  &#xA;It is best to place the output of the vol2 commands to a .txt file for better readability.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volatility was provided on the desktop of the investigation, so I started with running &lt;code&gt;volatility&lt;/code&gt; and the &lt;code&gt;pslist&lt;/code&gt; command, with the profile &lt;code&gt;WinXPSP2x86&lt;/code&gt; as suggested by the readme file, against the image file, then saving the output to a text file.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee of the Year</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/employee-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 01:45:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/employee-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a Friday evening when you were in a mood to celebrate your weekend, your team was alerted with a new RCE vulnerability actively being exploited in the wild. You have been tasked with analysing and researching the sample to collect information for the weekend team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-of-investigation&#34;&gt;Process of Investigation:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This challenge took some additional work before I could start work on the investigation. After downloading and extracting the contents of the challenge zip file, there was just one file, ‘recoverfiles.dd’.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reaper</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/reaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:01:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/reaper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our SIEM alerted us to a suspicious logon event which needs to be looked at immediately. The alert details were that the IP Address and the Source Workstation name were a mismatch. You are provided a network capture and event logs from the surrounding time around the incident timeframe. Correlate the given evidence and report back to your SOC Manager.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my write-up of the retired ‘Sherlock’ challenge, Reaper. Sherlocks are investigative challenges, to help develop and test defensive cybersecurity skills. Retired content on Hack The Box, has write-ups enabled, and I think that this would be a good opportunity to work through a challenge, and practice my documentation while working through the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Planets Prestige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/the-planets-prestige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 22:06:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cybersecurity/writeups/the-planets-prestige/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenario&#34;&gt;Scenario:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CoCanDa, a planet known as ‘The Heaven of the Universe’ has been having a bad year. A series of riots have taken place across the planet due to the frequent abduction of citizens, known as CoCanDians, by a mysterious force. CoCanDa’s Planetary President arranged a war-room with the best brains and military leaders to work on a solution. After the meeting concluded the President was informed his daughter had disappeared. CoCanDa agents spread across multiple planets were working day and night to locate her. Two days later and there’s no update on the situation, no demand for ransom, not even a single clue regarding the whereabouts of the missing people. On the third day a CoCanDa representative, an Army Major on Earth, received an email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
